One Pace Premium
Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
We, the pirates from Whitebeard's Second Division, will save Commander Ace!
Yeah!
Stop this!
Why are you all doing this for me?!
I'm your little brother!
You're so stupid, Luffy...
You too, Old Man!
Become my son!
What is it?
I'm...
... ready to accept whatever the future has in store for me.
I'll take the outstretched hand that saves me...
... or bow to the blade that punishes me.
I'm...
... not going to fight it anymore.
I'm sorry, everyone.
Resume the attack!
Fire!
Rubber-Rubber...
... Balloon!
The Prisoners of Impel Down
Right away, he's the center of attention!
That Straw Hat!
Captain Buggy! We can't let him outshine us!
Let's take Whitebeard's head already!
Very well, my friends! Let's do this!
But still, what's up with this crazy battlefield?
The marines and pirates here are all world-renowned!
It'd be better if I just lay low here...
Hey, Red-Nose!
Who're you callin' Red-Nose, you bastard?!
You wanna die or somethin'?!
Whitebeard?!
I thought I'd seen you somewhere before...
You're that brat who was on Roger's ship, aren't you?
That sure takes me back... So you're still alive?
Oh, crap! He's spotted me. I'm gonna die!
We're done for! We have no choice but to run!
W-Whitebeard! The great Whitebeard...
talked to the Captain! Amazing!
You really are a legendary pirate!
Don't act so impressed!
You'll catch the same hell as me!
Judging from all the prisoners you've brought along...
I suppose you've come to take my head?
Sure! Long time no see, huh? Now prepare yourself!
There's a limit to how far you can take this!
Really, now? I don't mind if you wanna take my head, but what're you gonna do afterward?
The Navy's forces are far too big for you to handle.
Actually, they're a bit much for me too. I've got my hands full here.
So, you wanna join up with me, and we'll take out the Navy as fellow pirates?
You can take my head after that.
Hang on a second! How much respect does Whitebeard have for you?
It's like they're equals!
I don't think he'd refer to his equal as a brat...
It's reckless of you to try and fight the Navy! Do you really think we can win?!
Well, if I get serious, yeah...
What happened to his common sense?
Seriously?
Ooh, I'm getting goosebumps!
I'm starting to feel like I can do this!
I can do it!
I can see it now! Buggy, king of the world!
If the two of us join forces, we can crush the Navy.
Please, stop it! You're so cool! Too cool!
Alright, Whitebeard! We'll back you up!
I will back you up!
Who is he?!
That's right! He's our Captain Buggy!
I can't believe how simple-minded these guys are.
Disregarding Red-Nose, the others behind him are pretty strong.
It'd be a pain to have to fight them.
So, now...
This is Whitebeard.
Is Squard there?
Old Man! Captain Squard is...
Huh? He was here a minute ago...
Seems we've lost sight of him.
He got carried away trying to impress you, Old Man...
That's too bad. Then, DeCalvan Brothers!
What is it, Old Man?
Old Man, what should we do?
Take command of all the pirate crews, and pass my orders on to them!
What? The Old Man? Alright, then I'll start on the right.
We'll take the left.
Sure. Got it.
We'll go to the right.
If that's what the Old Man wants...
My ship will go anywhere you want it to.
Squard? I don't see him anywhere... Is that right?
I'll go to the left.
Fleet Admiral Sengoku! The New World pirates are changing their attack pattern!
Yeah, they've scattered off in every direction.
They've started attacking the warships!
Well played, Whitebeard! He saw it coming.
Seems he's not falling for such an obvious trick.
I suppose I was too crude.
But sharp intuition won't be enough to stop fate!
You're kidding. Moriah's up against "Knight of the Sea", Jinbe?!
The Seven Warlords of the Sea are a vital part of our defense!
What good is it if they just kill each other?!
I'm more than a match for you, Moriah!
You wanna fight me, Jinbe?
Very well! I can't use my Zombie Warriors with you around, after all!
Keep moving, Luffy-kun! Don't waste any more time!
Thanks, Jinbe!
Our shadows are acting strange.
Marine shadows, give me your strength!
Now then, I'll be taking your shadow!
You'll spend eternity in the gloom at the bottom of the sea, Jinbe!
Hand over your shadow!
Fishman Karate...
Sharkskin Palm Block!
Shark Brick True Fist!
All that work and your shadows have left you...
You don't have enough skill.
Now step aside, Moriah.
I'm in a hurry.
Wait, dammit! The battle isn't over!
It's Straw Hat!
Get out of the way, Tashigi!
That hurt! You're...
Smokie!
That's right! His jutte has seastone inside of it!
Damn you...
Gear Second!
I will finish you!
Rubber-Rubber...
... Jet Gatling!
White Launcher!
He's a lot stronger than before!
Straw Hat!
He disappeared!
He's fast! Where'd he go?
It seems we've both grown stronger since we last met.
You can't defeat me with your ability.
Damn, it's that... jutte...
I finally understand...
... why Dragon saved you...
.... back in Loguetown. Straw Hat.
Dragon got in my way back then, but this time, you're not getting away!
D-Damn it...
Get your filthy hands off him!
She managed to hit me, even though I'm smoke...
But kicks shouldn't touch him...
That's...
The Pirate Empress protected Straw Hat!
Hancock! What are you playing at?!
Do you intend to quit being a Warlord, too?
Silence!
I am so infuriated, I don't care what you say!
How dare you beat and hold down my dearest?!
I will not let you live!
I have never been this angry before!
I will rip you apart and feed you to a beast!
So that was the Haki of the Kuja Tribe...
Hancock!
Yes!
You called me "Hancock" again!
Kuma! Kuma, come to vyour senses!
It's vme! Have vyou forgotten vmy face?!
Come to vyour senses, or Vi will fight back!
There's a limit to how much Vi can take!
I don't know what sort of history you two have,
but just give it up.
There's no point in talking to him, Emporio Ivankov, Commander of the Revolutionary Army.
Vyou're...
What are vyou saying?! What's going on?!
The man you know was probably named Bartholomew Kuma, right?
If you're thinking of the man once called Kuma the Tyrant...
... he's long dead.
What are vyou talking about?!
Kuma...
... is dead?!
W-What's going on? Why did
the Pirate Empress protect Straw Hat?
Take this.
This is the key to your brother's handcuffs.
Luffy's hand... Luffy's hand...
... touched mine!
Hancock!
You're the best! You're the best!
Thanks a lot! I owe you one!
I-It's alright! It's alright!
Do not worry about it, just...
... just keep moving forward, Luffy!
Oh, yeah!
Thanks!
No way! The Pirate Empress was defeated?!
He crushed her attack! He must have countered it with Sumo wrestling!
So this is what I heard so much about...
Marriage!
Perfume Femur!
Insolent one! I shall not let you past me!
Look at that! It's her Extreme Looking-Down Pose!
She's looking so far down her nose, she looks up instead!
Don't you know what'll happen if you get in the Navy's way?
No matter what I do, I shall be forgiven...
... for I am beautiful!
I'm really grateful for this! I owe her another one!
What'd you say?! Kuma is dead?!
Then who's the man standing in front of vme?
He's clearly alive! Don't be ridiculous!
Iva-chan!
It's that guy that looks like a bear!
Kuma: Bear
Iva-chan, do you know him?
Yeah... But he's acting strange.
It seems like the two of you have memories of Kuma,
but the Kuma you know, and this guy,
are two different people!
Different people? What's he talking about?
That's not possible! This is, without a doubt, the man who ate the Paw-Paw Fruit.
He's definitely Kuma! Speak to vme, Kuma!
It's useless, just like I've been saying. It doesn't matter how much you try to talk to him.
The other day,
... the Government's head scientist, Doctor Vegapunk, completed his final modifications on him...
... and transformed him into a perfect human weapon.
In other words, this isn't Bartholomew Kuma anymore!
Modifications? A weapon? What are vyou talking about?!
Basically, he was selected...
... by the Government's human weapon project to be a test subject. He volunteered for it himself.
They started with his arms...
... then his legs...
Leaving his consciousness intact,
the scientists replaced his body parts piece by piece, over a long period of time.
Stop lying! Kuma hates the World Government!
He would never...
... offer his own life to the Government!
Well, I don't know what kind of deal this guy had with the Government.
A couple of days ago, there was definitely some human left in him.
But now, he's lost all memory of being born human. He's as good as dead.
He's become a monster who only fights according to the Government's orders.
The Pacifista, PX-0!
The past is gone, you should just forget it!
Kuma! What happened to vyour body these past few years?!
Now that I think about it...
We will never meet again.
Farewell.
That's the last thing he said to me...
What's wrong, Kuma? It's vme! Ivankov!
W-Where is he? Where did he go?
He's dangerous, you guys! Be careful!
Pad Cannon
Damn vyou, Kuma!
Face...
... Spectrum!
Vyou scared yet?
Galaxy Wink!
How dare vyou attack vmy adorable Candies?!
Don't think Vi will hold back any longer!
Take this!
He sure is strong!
This is the first time anyone Vi have met has...
...forgotten...
... forgotten vmy face! That has never happened to vme before!
Oh... Yeah...
However!
Vi don't know if it's because vyour memories are gone,
but if vyou have even forgotten how terrifying Vi can be...
... then Vi will just beat the fear back into vyour body!
Prepare yourself!
He sure recovered quickly...
Vi will take care of him.
Vyou all, go help Straw-Hat-boy!
Roger that!
Now, let's go, Straw Hat!
Thanks for the help, Iva-chan!
Head for the execution platform!
Yeah!
Damn that cheeky Straw Hat!
Don't let him get too far ahead!
It's time to put Operation: "Make Captain Buggy Famous" into action!
Yeah!
If we succeed, the entire world will be forced to acknowledge my awesomeness!
Don't fall behind, and carry out my plan!
Will this plan really work?
Crocodile!
There's no end to them!
I was thrown pretty far from him...
We're not letting you get anywhere near the Old Man!
Don't get...
... in my way!
What a troublesome fellow... He just won't give up.
Brilliant Punk!
He's so big and fast...
Here he comes again.
The Commander of the Third Division, Diamond Jozu.
I'm impressed you got out, Croc-man.
How was your bath in the pond of blood?
Doflamingo. Don't interfere. You wanna die?
What an unpleasant thing to say...
How 'bout it? Wanna team up with me?
You think you're getting past?
Think you can stop us?
Go, Straw Hat!
Thanks!
Forgive me, Red Hair...
I will not go easy on him.
That's...!
... Hawk Eye!
Now then, fate.
Will the life of a promised child from the next generation... end here?
If not, how will he escape from this Black Blade?
Editing, Sewil
QC, Galaxy 9000, Pepperjack
Karaoke, KaitouYahiko
Timing, Galaxy 9000